

# Abegail B. Alcudia

Address Phone Number East Rembo, Taguig City 1643

mber 09621053667

Email

abegailalcudia@gmail.com



### About

I am a Front-end Developer with 5 years' experience. I am experienced in creating user interface, writing and testing codes, troubleshooting issues, implementing new features based on client feedbacks and converting mock-ups into usable web presence with HTML/CSS, JavaScript, JSON, JQuery languages, AngularJS and Angular framework.



#### Education

June 2016 - April 2018

**Bachelor of Science Major in Application Development** 

University of Makati

June 2014 - April 2016

Associate of Science Major in Application Development

University of Makati

June 2012 – April 2014 **High School Diploma** University of Makati



#### Personal

HTML/CSS/JavaScript – 5 years AngularJS – 4 years SCSS – 1 year Angular – 1 year



## Work Experience

(Feb 2018 - Oct 2022) Netlingo Support Services Inc.,

Makati City

Role: Web Developer

- Use markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages.
- · Develop, Maintain, and Improve websites.
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability.
- Converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, JSON coding and AngularJS.
- Coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery languages.
- Experience with responsive and adaptive design.
- Familiarity with CSS preprocessors such as SASS/SCSS.
- Ensuring websites are accessible across many platforms, including laptops and smartphones.
- Experience with graphic design applications such as Adobe Photoshop.
- Run debugging tools to eliminate flaws and glitches prior to publishing.
- Experience with cross-browser compatibility testing.

(Oct 2022 - Present) Accenture Inc.,

Quezon City

Role: Packaged App Development Analyst

- Project planning and analysis
- Creating UI/UX designs using Angular Material and Bootstrap 5
- Identifying and fixing bug, errors, and performance issues during development and after deployment.
- Customer support, addressing user inquiries, feedback and troubleshooting issues reported by users.
- Developed and maintained responsive web application using Angular framework.
- Experience with Typescript, HTML, CSS/SCSS.
- Oversaw technical issues and troubleshooting request to resolve user problems.